Viewers all over the world, right now open your heart for the Spirit of God to come.
I command that sickness -
there is no hiding place for that sickness -
wherever it is located, I command them out in the name of Jesus.
In your blood - out, in the name of Jesus!
In your kidney - out, in the name of Jesus!
In your liver - out, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips right now, viewers all over the world,
wherever you are, wherever that sickness is located in your body,
in your blood, kidney, liver, bones - I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Agree with me: I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Open your lips right now, open your heart for the Spirit to come, in the name of Jesus.
Here I am, heal me, Lord.
Here I am, deliver me, Lord, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Every chain satan might have used to connect you to himself -
chain of sickness, chain of affliction, whatever name it is called -
I break the chain, in the name of Jesus!
I can see the chains broken, in the name of Jesus.
I can see the connection broken, in the name of Jesus!
Connection of sickness - I can see it broken, in the name of Jesus!
Connection of affliction - I can see
it broken, in the name of Jesus!
I see it broken, in the name of Jesus!
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
I can see something about to leave you.
Press on, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to press on.
Something is about to leave your body; something is about to leave your blood.
Something is about to leave your kidneys.
Something is about to leave your liver.
Something is about to leave your bones.
Press on, in the name of Jesus!
By faith press on!
You must leave!
My body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
Holy Ghost!
My body is the temple of the Holy Ghost!
Press on!
You must leave!
Viewers all over the world, you are not left out!
You are included!
It is time right now.
Begin to pray, constantly pray in your heart.
Constantly pray in your heart, without ceasing.
Pray in your heart constantly.
This should be your habit from today.
This should be your habit day and night.
Constantly pray in your heart without ceasing.
Viewers all over the world, you are not excluded.
You are included!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Somebody touched me
Somebody touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
It must be Jesus
Jesus Christ touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
Constantly pray in your heart without ceasing.
This should be your habit from today.
Prayer is the key.
Don't forget: Your enemy loses no time in plotting against you.
You should lose no time in committing yourself.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
TT: Lizz ndungu 26/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 26/10/2018